So, for example, in this French concept, let's go to the voice mode.
I click it. And yes, it's hearing me, absolutely.
So, hello, chat, GPT. I am the most beginner when it comes to French,
and I'm trying to learn it, so I want to have the most beginner friendly conversation with you
right now in French. Are you ready?
Absolutely. So, as you see, he is talking in French.
No, please. Start talking to me in English. I am very, very, very, you know,
I'm just getting started with French, so we want to just practice the pronunciation
of a couple phrases.
Got it. Nowhere is it all. We'll keep it in English and focus on pronunciation.
If you have any specific phrases you want to practice, just let me know, and we can go step by step.
So, I was asking you with that command, and there are some phrases that you gave me,
like, Bonjour. So, am I pronouncing it right? Bonjour or Merci, Merci, buccou, you know,
or Silva play, which is, please, as I know.
Yes, you're on the right track. For Bonjour, you want to keep that on sound a bit nasal,
like Bonjour, and for Merci, it's just Merci. Nice and smooth. Merci, buccou, is Merci, buccou,
and Silva play is Silva play. You're doing great, keep it up.
So, I click and, and this voice mode conversation will end, and as you see, this is what we have
with the voice mode of chat GPT. It's also available, but not with the dictate option,
with this voice mode option over here. So, this is also what we have,